Inside the Patriot Stadium, a command center of stats, tracking hate speech online.
It shows...
Here's the anti-Semitic hate speech that they're tracking.
International law, people of Iran, blood of children, blood of tens, Nazi criminals, occupied West Bank.
It shows where it's coming from, the time of day, and how it's trending, especially among younger people.
We saw that not only is he an anti-Semitism growing across the country, it's disproportionately growing on college campuses and it has full support.
Which is part of the reason Kraft says he partnered with the United Negro College Fund and the Jewish organization Hillel International to host unity dinners throughout the country.
So, let's get to it!
Baruch College students Aiden Herzlinger and Akish El are among the more than 450 students who've attended at least one of the dinners.
What do you talk about at these dinners?
The dinners are about finding commonalities.
Common...
Free my mans, because he definitely looked like a hostage.
Talk about at these dinners.
The dinners are about finding commonalities, commonalities between the black community and the Jewish community.
So, we really talk about anything and everything.
It's not just about politics and opinions, it's about treating each other as humans.
We really talk about our families, why we have communities, and how our communities are similar, more than different.
Why Jewish students with black students?
Because historically we had that connection.
It's a connection that's gotten a lot done, and I think we can continue to get a lot done if we come together.
And when you heard those students talk about the history of blacks and Jews working together, consider this.
In June of 1964, three college students fight.
Wrap it up.
We're not going to do this.
Number one, our community does not have near the power that the Jewish community does.
We all know this.
Everybody knows this.
America has paid more reparations to the Jewish community in form of support for Israel than they paid the black Americans who were enslaved here for a crime that Americans didn't even fucking commit.
I'm not happy that Jewish people have been used as, you know, tools of imperialism, and I'm also not happy that so many people in the Jewish community have taken it upon themselves to let themselves be used that way.
And Robert Kraft is one of those people, so anything coming from his pro-Israel messaging has nothing to do with our blackness.
And the way that y'all can try to conflate that when you're actually the oppressors in this situation is sick as hell, and you can see that black man cringing because he knows what he is doing and his ancestors is telling him it's wrong.